It's braking hard due to the impact,
but I基本基
Good morning!
I'm going to change into my Akuma
costume from now on!
Today, I'm going to perform at Line
Cube Shibuya for the first time!
I'm going to read the comments of my
fans on my blog!
To the future members who have written
comments,
I'm looking forward to not revealing
those topics anymore,
like, I'll host event by Goto, I'll not
relax too much on today's blog..
Wait, it feels like I'm exposed?
I'm just joking right now.
I shouldn't say that.
New songs of Otoge Deliveristan,
CRUISHING
Good work everyone.
I wear costumes and do live
performances.
I'm excited about new things today.
I'm not going to announce all the new
things.
Everyone.
Are you a devil or an angel?
Which do you like?
Which one?
Thank you.
I'm wearing a rare hairstyle.
I may change my hairstyle.
I usually have a lot of hair down.
I'm wearing a lot of hair down.
I'm wearing a full-coffee outfit today.
Oh, there's also a taco rice!
Looks delicious.
Can you see it?
Today, I'm going to wear a special
version of Princess Princess Princess,
which is the number one princess.
I'm going to say a word to the judges,
Julia and Akisa.
Chicken rice and chicken.
Chicken rice.
Chicken.
What are you doing?
Study.
The strongest!
Wow, that's amazing!
Please use this.
The strongest!
Ketcha, the strongest!
Goal!
Eh, it wasn't the strongest?
The strongest!
Ah, it was the strongest.
Julia, the strongest!
I wish everyone bigger, but do not go.
Sorry, sorry
It's probably like this
Kanna singing
Shayoka used to dance this
Kanna sing...
It's cute
Thank you for watching.
I'll have the furukogi.
What's that?
It's a long rice cake, white rice cake,
and black rice cake.
Rice cake!
I have a bad memory.
I knew it.
I'll have the furukogi.
Bye bye.
It's falling.
What's wrong?
I'm going to take a picture.
This is the costume of the panel.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to my channel.
I'm wearing the costume of a devil.
I'm wearing a makeup from the
beginning.
I'm ready.
I'm going to dance.
Bye bye!
Let's do it like this.
I'm going to do it now.
Are you ready?
It's cute.
I'm going to do it.
Go! Go! Go!
It's long!
Please take a picture.
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
We are CHO-HONI. Thank you.
Live, drink, go on tomorrow 1 win
tomorrow highest voting
Thank you, sorry
It's okay
Please subscribe to our channel!
démo by 第 since 2001
Thank you.
Right hand, left hand, cha-cha-cha-cha-
cha-pa.
Toon, ton, ton.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
OK, OK, we're good.
Thank you for the rehearsal.
Thank you for the performance.
Thank you.
Go! Go!
It's so high!
It's easy to see.
I can see from above.
I see.
It's easy to see.
I'm happy.
Two more times.
I'm scared.
Yahoo!
Please subscribe to this channel.
It was a close call.
I don't feel high at all.
I don't feel like I'm going through.
The stairs are hard.
Let's do our best together.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Catch me!
Catch me, Julia's hand!
We arrived!
Good job!
Wow, beautiful!
It's scary!
It's good, isn't it? It's like a super
Halloween from above.
It's the scariest in the world.
Today, everyone is not doing it
anymore.
It's already Christmas.
When you come in from the back door,
you will be surprised.
When you get older, you will be 45
years old.
What is this?
You have to do it in front of the
camera.
I know.
One more time.
Let's go.
I'm going to open the door of the
audience.
Please speak English.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to open the door of the
audience.
If you don't give me a snack, I'll
tease you.
I have to tease you.
I'm going to open the door of the
audience.
I feel your presence in the morning
train
When the city lights are on, the scent
of love passes by
I'm still waiting for someone on the
bench
Remembering the days I spent with you,
I try drinking the juice I liked
It seems like I'm a little too much
alone, so I'll stay
Even now, I'm filled with fun memories,
they shine in the sky
I tried to reach out with both my hands
I tried my best, but
I'm sure I can't reach you anymore
I love you, I miss you
Every time I think of you like this,
the back of my chest feels tight
The rainbow-colored bench, I'm still
waiting
The bench is getting white
The scenery that's filled with a love
that won't disappear
The memories of you
I'm still waiting for someone
You're not coming back here anymore
I was able to say, I'll do my best,
I'll do my best
Stay by my side a little longer
I love you, I love you, I love you
I'll never forget, under the sky with
one eye open
I love you, I love you, I love you
I'm happy just by being like this
This kind of time is happiness
A rainbow-colored bench
Never changes
Benji! One, two, three, four, five!